Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
♪Let the daylight
pierce through the night♪
♪Unveiling the dazzling galaxy♪
♪This scorched remnant of myself♪
♪In this world of capricious tides♪
♪That perfect warmth♪
♪You are my only star♪
♪Heartless, obsessed, hopeful, loathing♪
♪How can we escape the regretful pasts♪
♪Watch the sky plunge into the sea♪
♪As dawn's first light
sketches the sky's outline♪
♪Entwined between our fingertips♪
♪When destiny weaves a brilliant net♪
♪Our souls are forged from the shards♪
=Flying Up Without Disturb=
=Episode 23=
After being sealed by Luanfeng Peak,
members of Hehuan Sect fled.
And this place has been abandoned.
But it's suitable
for our temporary stay.
No one knows about it,
and no one would come.
Kong Hou.
Someday we'll prove
you're not what they think.
What they care about
is never
what kind of person I am,
but my status.
Who am I really?
Kong Hou.
I-I'm not good with words,
but believe me.
To me, you are simply yourself,
the one I love
and protect
for the rest of my life.
I hope we
can stay together forever.
Look.
Come.
All surrounding plants have withered,
yet this flower still blooms.
So can we.
Ling Bo.
We've searched this entire area,
and found
nothing suspicious.
Okay, understood.
That dark cultivator is cunning.
Tracking her won't be easy.
Stay alert,
don't lose heart.
- Yes.
Ling Bo,
what's our next move?
Go back to report or...
Let's go back.
- Okay.
Lady Ling Bo.
You're here too?
We're coming under the head's orders
to find Master Zhong Xi.
Master Zhong Xi is missing?
He might have left
with Kong Hou.
We've searched
this area and found
no trace
of Master Zhong Xi.
Thank you for the information.
We'll search elsewhere.
Let's go.
(Oh no!)
(That direction leads to Hehuan Sect.)
(I can't let Xiao Dong go there.)
Ling Bo.
- Ling Bo.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
I twisted my ankle.
Let me see.
No need.
I've already checked that area.
Maybe go over there.
We might find
some clues there.
You people,
go check that area.
If you find
any traces,
report to me.
- Yes.
You guys go too.
More people mean better chances.
But your ankle...
I'm right here.
Don't worry.
It's fine.
If urgent,
send me a message.
- Yes.
Go.
Tell me,
where is Zhong Xi now?
I-I don't know.
You don't know?
Kong Hou has disappeared.
It must be your
and Zhong Xi's doing.
Tell me,
did Zhong Xi leave
with Kong Hou?
Say it.
I...
Y-You...
He's lost his mind.
Instead of stopping him,
you're being his accomplice.
You know he's crucial
to the entire Liuguang Sect
and the whole Lingyou Realm, right?
Besides, he's injured.
Y-You...
- Senior, watch out!
- Master.
Let go of me.
Listen,
if anything happens to him,
I'll hold you accountable.
How's it? Feeling better?
You shouldn't exhaust
your spiritual energy for me.
We regulate energy for each other.
It's not exhausting at all.
It actually eases me.
Don't worry.
Kong Hou.
Once this is over,
let's live in seclusion
in the mortal realm,
and ignore all these conflicts.
Okay?
Then,
after I recover.
You must be tired
from energy regulation.
I'll get you some food.
Wait here.
(We've)
(already escaped.)
(Maybe Zhong Xi is right.)
(We could live in seclusion,)
(spending our days)
(in peace.)
(But)
(why do I feel so scared?)
Careful.
Thanks.
(What to do?)
(I must hold him up)
(for one night.)
(Otherwise,)
(if he finds)
(Kong Hou and Master Zhong Xi,)
(all our efforts)
(will be wasted.)
Ling Bo.
Your injury
doesn't look severe.
What? It hurts!
I didn't bring
any medicine.
Endure it for now.
I'll send you back,
and then go meet the others.
No way.
This...
(Oh no.)
(What should I do?)
(I can't let him go.)
(Must hold him up.)
M-My...
My foot's injured, and it's hot...
Foot?
I feel dizzy and have headache.
Feeling dizzy?
Probably exhausted.
Ling Bo, you're a terrible liar.
You
always touch your ear when lying.
You saw through me.
How did you tell?
Never mind. I don't care.
That's the real you.
When you feigned weakness earlier,
I knew something was off.
Say it.
Why lied to me?
Holding me up
to stop me from finding Zhong Xi
and Kong Hou?
You and Lin Hu
helped them
escape, right?
Yes, we did it.
So what?
They wanted to strip
Kong Hou's spiritual roots.
I had to do something.
Besides,
Master Zhong Xi
is your master.
Can't you
trust him more?
Or do you
plan to capture me
and interrogate me?
Then you've misunderstood me.
I am
concerned about the Master.
Finding him
was only to verify
his safety.
I've learned
from you that he left safely,
and it reassures me.
I trust him.
And I
thought the same as you.
Kong Hou.
I need spiritual energy!
Spiritual energy!
Kong Hou, it's me.
No!
Zhong Xi, help me.
Zhong Xi.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't control myself.
It's alright.
It's over now.
Junior.
Senior.
Enough.
Just to confine me.
I'm even prepared for execution.
Think this scares me?
Only punishing you now
can we settle
the disputes.
Senior, just go.
They
won't stop
until they see me punished.
And I don't care.
My only concern now
is if Kong Hou
successfully escaped
the pursuers.
No news
is the best news.
It means she's not captured.
With Zhong Xi by her side,
they can support each other.
With Zhong Xi,
Kong Hou won't need
to tackle too much trouble alone.
Now focus on your cultivation.
I'll take care of the affairs.
Senior,
do you truly
have no questions for me?
Kong Hou
is a good disciple of Yunhua Sect.
Stay confined here with Tan Feng
to reflect on your actions.
Master.
Please don't be angry.
I just didn't want
Kong Hou to be wronged.
I merely wished Kong Hou...
Master.
Please don't blame Ling Hui.
Just blame me.
I failed to guide them.
Helping and trusting
your fellows
isn't wrong.
Actually,
I'm not a good master.
Failed to care for you.
Master, that's not true.
You taught me skills since childhood.
You showed me
the way to conduct myself.
I rarely showed
concern for you.
And I believed
letting you roam free was sufficient.
This forged your independence,
but also made you stubborn.
Actually,
if you told me about this matter,
I would've gone for you.
Master, I know you trust me.
And you trust Kong Hou too.
Please don't grieve.
I believe
everything will
come clear in the end.
Master.
When everything comes clear,
people will know
Kong Hou is innocent.
By then,
what Ling Hui and I did
was all worth it.
You all act with loyalty
and righteousness.
It's my Yunhua Sect's honor
to have disciples like you.
I also trust Kong Hou.
Everything will come to light.
Kong Hou...
Everything will be fine.
Master.
People are watching us closely now.
I must enforce justice impartially.
Rest within the barrier
for now.
I will tell you
about any update.
Rest assured.
Master will understand.
I'll stay by your side.
Zhong Xi, I'm sorry.
It doesn't matter.
It's all over.
You've grown.
When you saw me heal wounds this way,
you found it fascinating.
But...
Zhong Xi, I...
Alright.
I told you it's all over.
Besides,
that wasn't the real you.
But,
this will happen
frequently.
I'm scared.
If I'm not scared, why should you be?
Moreover,
there are so many shrews
in the world,
yet no
husband got killed by their wives.
Besides, I'm no ordinary one.
I'll get used to it.
What are you saying?
The previous line.
Well,
there are
so many shrews in the world.
Who is the shrew?
Who is...
I'm serious. No need to fear.
I'll stay with you.
Okay.
I understand.
Ling Bo.
For you.
What is this?
The Heavenly Cloud Manual.
You've been wanting to read it.
It took me a lot of effort to get it.
I already have one.
Keep it for yourself.
Why do you stare at me?
How do you
know I stare at you?
You...
When did you become
so eloquent?
Not at all.
I was just thinking
people say
marriage changes
a person.
But to be honest,
I never imagined
I'd live such a life.
To have a loved one by my side
is truly wonderful.
Kong Hou.
Tie me up.
Ling Bo.
I might carry you inside.
What? Why?
Don't misunderstand.
I mean,
we need a plausible reason
to return together, right?
You
twisted your ankle,
and then I helped you return.
Otherwise, gossip might spread.
Why aren't they back yet?
Ling Bo
said to pretend it.
Why do
you two return together?
Why are you carrying her?
Put me down first.
Okay.
I met her in the outskirts.
And she got her foot injured.
So I carried her back.
Injured? Where?
(This act is too obvious.)
(If I care about her,)
(she'll laugh at me.)
Lady Ling Bo,
you should practice more.
Getting injured that easily
won't do.
None of your business.
What?
Last time, you...
What are you two talking about?
Just drop me here.
You may return.
Alright.
I'll go back to report.
W-What do you mean?
Just leave.
Wait.
Don't we leave together?
I need to chat with Ling Bo.
You go ahead.
I'm tired. I'm going back.
Let me support you.
Well...
Master is waiting.
Go back now.
Wait, you...
Be careful.
Careful.
What could he possibly chat
with Lady Ling Bo?
He...
Be careful.
Where exactly are you injured?
I'm okay.
Wait, Ling Bo.
I know some healing arts.
If needed,
I could treat you.
See? I'm okay.
Are you truly okay?
Alright. I need rest.
You may leave.
Well, I have a question.
Did you really stay with Xiao Dong
last night?
Yes.
H-How could you?
What's wrong?
I was worried
Xiao Dong might find
Kong Hou and Zhong Xi,
so I pretended to twist my ankles.
Well,
t-that's still inappropriate.
You shouldn't
let him carry you back.
If needed,
you could've messaged me,
and I'll fetch you.
Or had
your fellows
fetch you.
You're quite good at it.
Told me to message you
or have my fellows
fetch me.
Xiao Dong was right beside me.
If I did that,
that would seem
suspicious.
Well, you're right.
Fine. Since you're okay,
I'll leave.
Rest early.
Take good rest.
Lin Hu.
Where has the Master gone?
How much do you know?
If you ask me,
I know some.
If you ask me to tell, I know nothing.
Stop confusing me.
You released the Master?
W-What?
Whose side are you on?
Now even you
are targeting Young Master?
Fine. I'll tell you.
I released Young Master.
If you want to snitch,
go ahead.
I accept any punishment.
Okay.
The Master was released
by you and Ling Bo, right?
What?
Why involved Ling Bo?
I've told you
I released Young Master.
Why involved her?
Okay, I believe you.
You've been visiting Ling Bo every day.
Do you have
a crush on her?
What?
I visit her because
we have matters
to discuss.
We always argue
when we're together.
Have a crush on her?
Fine, I believe you.
You'd better
tell me the truth.
Because I like Ling Bo.
What?
D-Don't lie to me.
You have a crush on someone.
I'm not lying.
My crush is Ling Bo.
Well...
The girl you mentioned
was Ling Bo?
Yes.
Ling Bo.
Knocking on my door at this hour,
you better have
a proper reason.
I wanted to check if there are
bugs in your room.
Wait.
I mean it.
Don't think I'm overreacting.
At this hour,
those bugs could be hiding
under tables, beds,
or even your pillow.
You can't see them now.
If one crawls over you,
you'll be crying.
Lin Hu.
Who said that
it's inappropriate for me
to stay with Xiao Dong last night?
Do you think
your coming here
is appropriate?
I...
Enough.
No bugs in my room.
You may go.
I have a question.
Well,
did you date Xiao Dong before?
Are you here to gossip?
Coming here so late
just to ask that?
No! I'm just concerned about you.
What?
This is my private matter.
None of your business.
Besides,
what if I did?
What if I didn't?
Who are you to me?
Why would I tell you?
Enough. Go back to bed.
This is inappropriate.
Wait.
I...
I haven't finished speaking.
Bugs?
You're just jealous.
Still deny it? How childish.
Why am I smiling?
What's so funny?
He's being jealous.
What's it to do with me?
Kong Hou.
Every time,
he gets hurt because of me.
What if someday,
I lose control of myself?
(Are you getting)
(less able to control)
(your spiritual energy?)
(Want to learn how?)
(Come find me.)
(You can find me.)
Master.
What's
the matter?
Sit down first.
Master.
Is there something important?
I have sword practice soon.
I asked you to sit,
so you wouldn't be startled.
Master, what's wrong?
Ling Bo.
Tell me,
have you truly broken up
with that Xiao Dong?
Why mention him suddenly?
There's nothing
between us anymore.
Seriously?
Then why did he
suddenly come to me?
To propose a marriage to you.
What?
Propose marriage?
Xiao Dong.
Ling Bo.
Did you
propose a marriage to me?
Yes.
What's wrong with you?
Ling Bo.
I can't lose you again.
I've wasted many
chances and time already.
This time,
if your master consents,
we'll marry soon.
My master's consent means nothing.
I haven't agreed.
I know you're still mad at me
that I didn't come to you back then
and took
your angry words seriously,
making us part ways.
I am not.
No more angry words, Ling Bo.
I did speak angry words back then,
but I am telling you
the honest words now.
I can understand
why you're mad at me.
Had I been...
Had I been
more resolute,
you wouldn't leave me,
and I...
Why don't you listen to me?
I was ignorant before,
but now,
I won't give up on you.
Ling Bo.
My sister.
Who's your sister?
If not my sister,
why come to see me?
Zhong Xi
has real skill.
I feared
you'd suffer
from unstable spiritual energy.
But even so,
he's not worthy to marry you.
Enough talk.
He's not involved.
I love him,
so I won't stay
to hurt him.
Tell me,
how exactly
can I control this dark energy?
Come with me,
and I'll tell you.
(If I stay here,)
(I might)
(accidentally hurt Zhong Xi.)
(And I still didn't)
(clarify my origins.)
(If he's up to)
(something evil,)
(I'd better go with him)
(to find out.)
Fine. I'll go with you.
How dare you, Jiusu!
Where are you going? Let her go.
Taking Kong Hou home.
Considering your care
for her these days,
I'll spare you
today.
Moreover,
are you blind?
Do you think
I kidnap her?
Kong Hou
came with me willingly.
Impossible.
Kong Hou.
You promised
to leave this place
and live in seclusion with me.
Who promised you?
I said,
after I recover.
But
when I'm with you,
I can't even
control my spiritual energy.
My pain only grows.
But my brother
can ease my pain,
so I must go with him.
Kong Hou.
Zhong Xi.
Given
our past bond,
I'll be honest.
I am the Dark Sovereign's daughter.
My bloodline defines me.
I and you guys
are at odds.
I have my path to go.
Righteous sects oppressed my kin.
And I will reclaim our honor.
Kong Hou.
Don't trust him.
Awesome, Kong Hou!
Not blinded by affection
and emotions.
Why do you
bring me here?
You are a dark cultivator.
This is where you belong.
You didn't know it before.
But now,
why still talking nonsense?
Don't forget
we are family.
No way.
I understand
you're mad at me.
After all, we have
past misunderstandings.
What?
Exactly.
Had I known you were my sister,
I'd never have harmed you.
So you can harm
righteous cultivators?
Righteous?
Such labels
mean nothing.
You've committed evil deeds.
So you'd say that.
You don't understand.
And I'll
tell you one day.
One day?
Then I'll
be all ears
to your lies.
You're quite composed.
I saw you're lively and mischievous,
and doubted
your capabilities.
In that case,
why bother
bringing me here?
If you hate hearing it,
I'll stop.
I don't
expect you to accept me now.
Rest now.
Later, I'll introduce everyone.
Everyone?
Who's everyone?
Our kin, of course.
Now that you're here.
You'll lead our kin
to forge a new era.
I believe
everything will change.
This is
the Yunhua Sect's...
Your Eminence.
Why do you bring
a righteous sect's disciple?
Stop
the commotion.
Father's dying wish
was for Kong Hou
becoming our Sovereign.
All these years,
I have been too incompetent
to bring her back.
Now,
Kong Hou has returned.
From now on,
she shall be our Yueluo Clan's
newly appointed Sovereign.
We must all wholeheartedly support her.
No defiance tolerated.
- Well...
Right.
Your Eminence,
this woman
was cultivated by
the hypocritical sect.
She doesn't side with us.
She even injured you.
Why are you doing this?
I wonder why too.
You're abandoning
your position as Dark Sovereign
and handing it over to me?
You possess the Five Spiritual Roots,
with excellent talents.
The Dark Sovereign title
rightfully belongs to you.
What? Don't you want it?
Since I'm here,
it makes no difference to me.
But your people might not be convinced.
Exactly. So what?
You're just here
to spy on us.
Well?
Anyone else?
Starting today,
I am your Sovereign.
Your Eminence,
please take your seat of honor.
- All hail the Sovereign!
♪Roaming with the wind♪
♪Wandering about♪
♪A final ember of warmth abides♪
♪Absurd plots unfold♪
♪Mere spectators♪
♪Footprints left on shores♪
♪Fickle kisses burn♪
♪Withering in an instant♪
♪Lanterns glow, depicting her grace♪
♪Like rusted locks♪
♪Chaining our memories♪
♪Only scars remain♪
♪Breaking from worldly desires♪
♪Dreams shattered, but reality rolls on♪
♪Letting down my guard,
drowning in the perilous love♪
♪You stole my heart♪
♪Vows scatter with the air♪
♪All the wounds will heal with care♪
♪Love is mystery♪
♪So be it♪
♪She blazes uncontrolled♪
♪A sickness of the soul♪
♪Cold nights take their toll♪
♪So be it♪
♪All efforts go unrewarded♪
♪Breaking from worldly desires♪
♪Dreams shattered, but reality rolls on♪
♪Letting down my guard,
drowning in the perilous love♪
♪You stole my heart♪
♪Vows scatter with the air♪
♪All the wounds will heal with care♪
♪So be it♪